softplatz.net 2009-03-14

# Privacy - www.softplatz.com

## Overall privacy statement

We take your privacy seriously. Because we gather certain types of information about our users, we want to help you understand the terms and conditions surrounding the collection and use of that information. This privacy statement discloses the types of information we gather, how we use it, and how to correct or change it. These privacy practices apply to the Web site that you were viewing when you clicked through to this policy, which is operated directly by us, by our partner, or by our affiliate.

## Collected information

We collect personally identifiable information, such as your name, email address, postal address (for developers only), phone number (for developers only) when you provide it to us. We may also receive information about you from other sources and add it to the information you provided to us.

## Our cookies policy

Your Internet browser has a feature called cookies, which stores small amounts of data on your computer about your visit to any of our sites. You do not need to have cookies turned on to visit most of our sites, although active participation in certain areas of our sites may require cookies. Cookies alone tell us nothing about who you are unless you specifically give us personally identifiable information, in which case we use the information to enhance your services in the ways described below. By adjusting your settings on your browser, you may elect not to allow cookies to be collected.

We use cookies and tracking technologies in a variety of ways, including: 

  1. Keeping count of return visits to our site or our advertisers' or partners' sites 
  2. Accumulating and reporting anonymous, aggregate, statistical information on Web-site and advertisement usage 
  3. Determining which features our overall user population likes best 
  4. Displaying the most appropriate advertising or content based on your interests 

## Usage of the collected information

We use the information we gather for the following purposes: 

  1. To customize the advertising and the content you see 
  2. To fulfill your requests for certain products and services 
  3. To send you the answer on the feedback you made 

## Information sharing policy

We do not share the personalized information we gather with any company or person, except when it is required by law. Non-personal information (such as agregate stats) can be shared upon request of some company or person.

## E-mail unsubscription option

Each e-mail sent from us is provided with subscription management instructions. You are able either to unsubscribe or to re-subscribe to our e-mail notifications at any time.

## Privacy Policy changes

Any modifications to our privacy practices will be reflected first within this area of this Web site. If there is a material change in our privacy practices, we will indicate on our sites that our privacy practices have changed and provide a link to the new privacy statement.
